<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CSS on kencho51</title>
    <link>https://kencho51.github.io/tags/css/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CSS on kencho51</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>kencho51</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 11:21:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kencho51.github.io/tags/css/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 28/9-2/10/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/28-9-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 11:21:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/28-9-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Yii2 JavaScript, FCC CSS, FCC Clean Code, YouTube  Todo  Add link preview #61 remove dataset publisher option from admin pages #381 To start a new project, user story  Done  PR #507 Comment on #375  Reference  Yii2 Database migration</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 21-24/9/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/21-9-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 10:01:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/21-9-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Yii2 JavaScript, FCC CSS, FCC Clean Code, YouTube  Todo  To start a new project, user story  Done  Merged PR Delete button #503 Closed and merged PR Pagination #495  Reference</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 14-18/9/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/14-9-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 09:26:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/14-9-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  JavaScript, FCC CSS, FCC Clean Code, YouTube  Learning progress  Finished 80% of Java Algorithm and Data Structure Certification.  Todo  Finish no ability to remove file attributes #457  Done  Follow up PR Pagination #495  Update the pressEnterKey to detectEnterKeyPress Clean up the dataset-view.feature   For PR Delete button #503  Create actionDeleteAttr in the controller class for the delete function Create a Delete button in the _form file of view class that calls js-delete function Create a js-delete function that calls action deleteAttr and add window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 7-11/9/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/7-9-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 14:40:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/7-9-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  JavaScript, FCC CSS, FCC Clean Code, YouTube  Learning progress  Finished 75% of Responsive Web Design Certification Finished 70% of Java Algorithm and Data Structure Certification.  Todo Done  Follow up PR View files from large db #437  Create a more generic I hit return behat scenario. Remove commented codes. Delete PhantomJS dependence and update chrome browser window size to window-size=1024,768   Follow up no ability to remove file attributes #457  Update actionUpdate, but get Error 500 Trying to get property of non-object error.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>