<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>php on kencho51</title>
    <link>https://kencho51.github.io/tags/php/</link>
    <description>Recent content in php on kencho51</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>kencho51</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 10:58:32 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kencho51.github.io/tags/php/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bdd</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/bdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 10:58:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/bdd/</guid>
      <description>What is Behavior Driven Development?  Behavior Driven Development (BDD) is a branch of Test Driven Development (TDD).
  BDD uses human-readable descriptions of software user requirements as the basis for software tests.
 Introduction of BDD from Konstantin Kudryashov, the creator of Behat YouTube
What is gherkin language?  Gherkin is a Business Readable, Domain Specific Language created specifically for behavior descriptions. Gherkin is a whitespace-oriented language that uses indentation to define structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP_CodeSniffer</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/phpcodesniffer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 14:28:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/phpcodesniffer/</guid>
      <description>What is PHP_CodeSniffer? PHP_CodeSniffer is a set of two PHP scripts:
 phpcs script that tokenizes PHP, JavaScript and CSS files to detect violations of a defined coding standard. phpcbf script to automatically correct coding standard violations.  Installation Follow here
Usage   Checking files and folders
vendor/bin/phpcs /path/to/code
  Printing summary report
vendor/bin/phpcs --report=summary /path/to/code
  Specifying a Coding Standard
vendor/bin/phpcs --standard=PEAR /path/to/code/myfile.php
  List all installed coding standards</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP date times</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/phpdatetimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 12:03:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/phpdatetimes/</guid>
      <description>What is timestamp? A timestamp is the number of seconds from January 1, 1970 at 00:00.
&amp;lt;?php //output number of seconds from Jan 1, 1970 at 00:00. echo time(); echo date(&amp;#34;d/m/y&amp;#34;).&amp;#34;\n&amp;#34;; $now = getdate(); echo $now[&amp;#34;hours&amp;#34;]+8; //print_r ($now);  // &amp;#39;z&amp;#39; is indexed from 0, so it is necessary to add 1. $numDays = date(&amp;#34;z&amp;#34;, mktime(0,0,0,12,31,2020))+1; $numWeeks = date(&amp;#34;W&amp;#34;, mktime(0,0,0,12,31,2020)); echo &amp;#34;There are $numDaysdays and $numWeeksweeks in 2020.\n&amp;#34;; How to display the current date/time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 29/6-3/7/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/29-6-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 09:55:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/29-6-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Codeception in PhpStorm Functional test Unit test  Todo    Done  PR Issue #460, functional test for admin site access. Issue #448   Problem  Install codeception to PhpStorm is difficult, a lot of env param is invloved.  Reference </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Codeception</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/whatiscodeception/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 13:41:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/whatiscodeception/</guid>
      <description>What is Codeception?  Codeception is a framework written in PHP for testing application and its multi-featured test framework powered by famous PHPUnit Framework.
  It can manage Unit, Functional and Acceptance for web application.
 How to create a Unit Test? Testing pieces of code before coupling them together.
It creates a new ExampleTest file located in the tests/unit directory.
php vendor/bin/codecept generate:test unit Example
Run the newly created test with this command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP standards</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/phpstandards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 11:35:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/phpstandards/</guid>
      <description>What is PSR?  PSR is a standard established by PHP-FIG(PHP Framework Interop Group).
  PSR consists of several standards such as PSR-1, PSR-2 and PSR-4.
  PSR-0 and PSR-4 are coding standards for PHP’s autoloaders, PSR-1 and PSR-2 are basic coding standards.
  PHP code MUST use only UTF-8 without BOM(Byte Order Mark).
 PSR-1 Basic Coding Standard, defines basic parts of PHP coding  Only &amp;lt;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 15-19/6/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/15-6-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 09:56:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/15-6-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Docker TDD PHP standard PHPUnit Codeception Yii1.1 and Yii2  Todo  Issue #423 Issue #440 Issue #425  Problem Done  Created PR for issue #291 PHPUnit doc, YouTube PHP Standards: PSR-1, PSR-2 and PSR-12  Reference </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 8-12/6/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/8-6-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 09:25:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/8-6-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Docker PostgreSQL OOP progress Yii1.1 framework utterances  Todo       Problem  For Issue #291, the codes in local develop branch is huge different from that in production server, a cascade of changes will be needed. Yii1.1 blog update Home page from /site/index to /site/post in /layouts/main.php  Done  Fixed issue #421 Fixed issue #441 Issue #291  Reference  How to add Utterances in Hugo post utterances  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yii1.1 for beginners</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/yiiforbeginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 15:05:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/yiiforbeginners/</guid>
      <description>What is Yii Model-View-Controller architecture? MVC schema
 Model   defines relations among data in DB and rules that must be followed when saving data to DB. It also gives us tools to read/save data from/to DB.
 View   shows data to user. It doesn’t write to DB or count difficult things. It just receives data and shows them using HTML, CSS, JS, etc.
 Controller   processes and changes the data, handles user’s actions, decides, counts, thinks and calls models and views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a blog using Yii1.1</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/projects/howtobuildablogusingyii1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 10:10:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/projects/howtobuildablogusingyii1/</guid>
      <description>Aim To familiarize the framework of Yii 1.1.
How  The steps can be found here The source code is stored at github repo  Docker container for Nginx and PHP=FPM webserver, link Steps to note  Download the Yii 1.1 source code at here Unpack the compressed file and move to dockerfolder/app
tar -xvzf yii-1.1.22.bf1d26.tar.gz Rename the folder name to yii-1.1.22 Go to the framework folder to create a skeleton application by</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 1-5/6/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/1-6-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 09:39:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/1-6-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Docker Yii1.1 framework PostgreSQL OOP progress  Todo  Use Yii 1.1 to build a blog  Done  Fixed issue#433. Fixed issue#436. Finished buiding yii 1.1 blog Made a pull request for issue #421  Reference  For Docker:  13 Best Docker Tutorials to Learn Docker Container Docker for beginners Docker tutorial for Beginners, YouTube    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yii 2.0 - Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/yiiprogress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 11:05:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/yiiprogress/</guid>
      <description>Install Composer via Composer on Mac OS X curl -sS https://getcomposer.org/installer | php sudo mv composer.phar /usr/local/bin/composer
Install Yii composer create-project --prefer-dist yiisoft/yii2-app-basic basic
Installing Assets Add the following lines to /basic/composer.json
&amp;#34;replace&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;bower-asset/jquery&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;gt;=1.11.0&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;bower-asset/inputmask&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;gt;=3.2.0&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;bower-asset/punycode&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;gt;=1.3.0&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;bower-asset/yii2-pjax&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;&amp;gt;=2.0.0&amp;#34; }, Verify the Installation Go into the basic/
php yii serve
User browser to access:
http://localhost:8080/
CHeck if the minimum requirements are met by running cd basic
php requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OOP</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/oop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:13:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/oop/</guid>
      <description>What is OOP? Object-oriented programming is a style of coding that allows developers to group similar tasks into classes. This helps keep code following the tenet &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t repeat yourself&amp;rdquo; (DRY) and easy-to-maintain.
 Object-oriented programming is a style of coding that allows developers to group similar tasks into classes.
 What is a class?  A blueprint for a house. It defines the shape of the house on paper, with relationships between the different parts of the house clearly defined and planned out, even though the house doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 25-29/5/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/25-5-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 11:22:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/25-5-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Using Yii to build a blog system PHP  To-do Done  Yii 2 crash course Update issue 160
2.1 update the link url to relate link, not the production server ones Yii the Definitive guide to Yii 2.0
3.1 created a sqlite database
3.2 tried Gii to create CRUD models and actions The Definitive Guide to Yii 1.1 Update portal address in contact us page for Issue #436  however the image of the location map not showing    Resources  Yii Best Yii Best Free Yii2 Tutorials OOP concepts OOP code examples  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP progress</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/phpprogress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 17:48:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/phpprogress/</guid>
      <description>Learning PHP at Codecademy Topics   String and variables - Done
  Number - Done
  Functions - Done
  Intro to Built-in PHP functions - Done
 find variable types
gettype(); var_dump(); string functions
strrev();strtolower(); strtoupper(); str_repeat(); substring
substr_count(); number function
abs(); round(); generating random numbers
rand(); getrandmax(); ceil(); documentation
str_pad(); check value in array
in_array(&amp;quot;valuetocheck&amp;quot;, $array)    Ordered Arrays
 can be integer or string or any data type $my_array = array(); or $my_array=[]; returns the array length</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 18-22/5/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/18-5-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 14:00:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/18-5-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  php Yii  To-do  Study github issues.  start issue#160  url for Editorial board url for github update the content     Start PHP Numbers at Codecademy. Start Yii, learn how to build a blog system.  Done  Personal hugo page released. Finined PHP course at Codecademy. Made pull request for issue 160  Resources  For Yii, link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 10-15/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/10-5-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/10-5-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  php docker  To-do Study github issues assigned by Peter Github workflow:
	1. git checkout develop 2. git branch ken_issues 3. change the source code 4. test after change using docker 5. git add, commit, push 6. git message in present imperative tensehu 7. create a pull request on issue# </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 4-8/5/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/4-5-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/4-5-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn Start learning github, docker, php
To-do  Set up account stuff  Done  Configuration
1.1 zsh
2. install homebrew, wget, curl 3. Github, branch, pull, merge link
4. vimtutor
5. markdown syntax Config computer, zshrc, vimrc, github, docker Fork gigadb-website  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
