<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PostgreSQL on kencho51</title>
    <link>https://kencho51.github.io/tags/postgresql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PostgreSQL on kencho51</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>kencho51</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 10:25:23 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kencho51.github.io/tags/postgresql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Postgresql</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/postgresql/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 10:25:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/postgresql/</guid>
      <description>What is PostgreSQL?  PostgreSQL is an enterprise-class open source database management system. It supports both SQL for relational and JSON for non-relational queries. PostgreSQL supports advanced data types and advance performance optimization.
 Key features  Compatible with various platforms using all major languages and middleware It offers a most sophisticated locking mechanism Support for multi-version concurrency control Compliant with the ANSI SQL standard Full support for client-server network architecture Log-based and trigger-based replication SSL Standby server and high availability Object-oriented and ANSI-SQL2008 compatible Support for JSON allows linking with other data stores like NoSQL which act as a federated hub for polyglot databases  MySQL vs PostgreSQL    MySQL PostgreSQL     The MySQL project has made its source code available under the terms of the GNU License, and other proprietary agreements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 8-12/6/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/8-6-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 09:25:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/8-6-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn  Docker PostgreSQL OOP progress Yii1.1 framework utterances  Todo       Problem  For Issue #291, the codes in local develop branch is huge different from that in production server, a cascade of changes will be needed. Yii1.1 blog update Home page from /site/index to /site/post in /layouts/main.php  Done  Fixed issue #421 Fixed issue #441 Issue #291  Reference  How to add Utterances in Hugo post utterances  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
