<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OOP on kencho51</title>
    <link>https://kencho51.github.io/tags/oop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OOP on kencho51</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>kencho51</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 12:48:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kencho51.github.io/tags/oop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OOP basics</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/oopbasics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 12:48:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/oopbasics/</guid>
      <description>Here is the OOP crash course video: And here is the Introduction to programming and Computer Science video Reference OOP programming basics Introduction to programming and computer science </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 8-12/6/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/8-6-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 09:25:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/8-6-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn Docker PostgreSQL OOP progress Yii1.1 framework utterances Todo Problem For Issue #291, the codes in local develop branch is huge different from that in production server, a cascade of changes will be needed. Yii1.1 blog update Home page from /site/index to /site/post in /layouts/main.php Done Fixed issue #421 Fixed issue #441 Issue #291 Reference How to add Utterances in Hugo post utterances </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OOP</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/oop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:13:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/oop/</guid>
      <description>What is OOP? Object-oriented programming is a style of coding that allows developers to group similar tasks into classes. This helps keep code following the tenet &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t repeat yourself&amp;rdquo; (DRY) and easy-to-maintain.
Object-oriented programming is a style of coding that allows developers to group similar tasks into classes.
What is a class? A blueprint for a house. It defines the shape of the house on paper, with relationships between the different parts of the house clearly defined and planned out, even though the house doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn, todo and done 25-29/5/20</title>
      <link>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/25-5-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 11:22:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kencho51.github.io/jobs/25-5-20/</guid>
      <description>Learn Using Yii to build a blog system PHP To-do Done Yii 2 crash course Update issue 160
2.1 update the link url to relate link, not the production server ones Yii the Definitive guide to Yii 2.0
3.1 created a sqlite database
3.2 tried Gii to create CRUD models and actions The Definitive Guide to Yii 1.1 Update portal address in contact us page for Issue #436 however the image of the location map not showing Resources Yii Best Yii Best Free Yii2 Tutorials OOP concepts OOP code examples </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
